{"data":[{"question":"A worker on an exhausting job is an ___ worker.","a":"exhaust","b":"exhausting","c":"to exhaust","d":"exhausted","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A participle phrase will begin with a present or past participle. If the participle is present, it will dependably end in ing. Likewise, a regular past participle will end in a consistent ed.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The dog, ___, will make a good watch dog.","a":"to train properly","b":"training properly","c":"properly to train","d":"trained properly","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase introduces a main clause, separate the two sentence components with a comma","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I started the clock ___.","a":"to go","b":"going","c":"gone","d":"to be gone","answer":"2","explain":"- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action\n\n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Before ___ to the college, he had to go through an examination.","a":"admitting","b":"to admit","c":"being admitted","d":"having been admitted","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase introduces a main clause, separate the two sentence components with a comma ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"A beggar was dragging his weary feet with many kids ___ behind.","a":"following","b":"to follow","c":"followed","d":"being followed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ with mine, your audio components are rather expensive.","a":"Comparing","b":"To compare","c":"To be compared","d":"Compared","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase introduces a main clause, separate the two sentence components with a comma","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":" How was the concert last night? \" It was ___ \"","a":"disappointing","b":"disappointed","c":"disappoint","d":"disappointment","answer":"1","explain":"Very good! Correc\n\n- Disappointing: when word describled is non-person\n\n- Disappointed: when word describled is person","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The room is crowded, but there are ___.","a":"a few seats to leave","b":"few seats left","c":"a few seats left","d":"few seats to leave","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase introduces a main clause, separate the two sentence components with a comma","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"All the students felt ___ listening to his lecture.","a":"bored","b":"boring","c":"to bore","d":"bore","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Boring: when word described is non-person \n- Bored: when word described is person ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The President was sitting on the chair ___ by his supporters.","a":"surrounding","b":"to surround","c":"surrounded","d":"surround","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}